Guide to the Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records, 1970-2012.
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records,
- Series II: Events, Projects, and Services
  - 1971-1984
    - Political Work
      - Anti-discrimination statements, 1977? (Box 4, Folder 43-44)
      - City Council Candidate Attitude forms, 1979? (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Political survey, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Tsongas, Senator, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Gay Alliance election recommendations, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Other Local Organizations
      - NYC gay organizations- Long Island, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - NYS gay organizations, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Organizations- Rochester, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Gay Political Caucus, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Gay Political Caucus, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - University of Rochester- GLF- concert materials, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Coalition for Justice in the Federal Budget, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Coalition for Lesbian/Gay Rights NYC, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - FLGC Genesee Valley Meeting Minutes, 1/7/1982 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - RGTF (Rochester Gay Task Force), 1972-1979 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - RGTF, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - RGTF Stationary/Envelopes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Gay Activists Alliance, NY, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - "The Center" materials, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - "The Center" proposals, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Gay Brotherhood of Rochester office info., Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Gay Brotherhood of Rochester Miscellaneous (includes original membership list), 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Gay Brotherhood of Rochester by-laws, financial statement, 1973, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Gay Brotherhood of Rochester coordinating council minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Gay Brotherhood of Rochester Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
      - Gays for Political Action, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Gay Alliance info., Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Gay Liberation Front- legal and political action committee notes, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Gay Liberation Front Miscellaneous, 1971-1974? (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Gay Liberation Front Miscellaneous, 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Gay Activists Alliance press release re: disbanding of the Alliance, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - GROW press release, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
      - Press release- BWMT, GAGV, RGTF, GROW, 1977, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Report of the OMEGA treasury, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1974, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - NYSCGO (New York State Coalition of Gay Organizations), 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - NYSCGO, 1973, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - NYSCGO general meeting, Oct. 1973 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - NYSCGO legislative resource packet, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - NYSCGO meeting attendance, Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - NYSCGO conference- Rochester, Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - New York State Gay/Lesbian Conference Conference Report, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - NYS Gay/Lesbian Conference, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - NYS Gay/Lesbian Conference volunteer packet, Undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - GROW (Gay Revolution of Women) materials, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - c. 1986-2014(Second Donation)
    Materials containing sensitive information have been restricted until 2040 and placed in Boxes 34, 63-65.
    - General Programming
      - LGBT Awareness at Kodak, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 1)
        "Who am I?" Intro exercise, handwritten note. Some materials undated.
      - SUNY Brockport Social Work Program Guides and Manuals, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Surveys of Medical Providers, c. 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Gaysource Infoline, c. 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Lending Library, Undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - National Coming Out Day Events, c. 1996-2000 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Senior Group, c. 1999-2000 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Family Fest w/ Writers & Books, c. 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Men's and Women's Socials, c. 1997 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Family Programs, c. 1999-2002 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Stronger Together: NCBI, c. 1994-1998 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Community Center Forums, c. 2002 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - BI Support Group, c. 1996-2000 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Claiming the Promise, c. 2002 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Next Step Group for Young Adults, Undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Strengthening Ourselves, c. 1989-1994, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Pillow Talk, c. 2003 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Next Step Group, 1999-2003 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Couples Group, c. 1998-2000 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Dating Workshop, c. 2001-2003 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Being Gay at Work, c. 2002 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Breaking the Ice, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - TASS Program, c. 1999 -2003 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Resources, c. 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 13)
        Mainly youth related. Includes a grant contract.
      - Queer Youth Advocacy Network, 2000-2001` (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Brighton Parent Report, c. 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 15)
        Includes and issure of Alternative Family Magazine.
      - Queer Upstate Youth Providers, 2002 2001 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Center Forum, Undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Strengthening Ourselves, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 13)
        Includes Registration forms and evaluations for Breaking the Ice and Bi Support Group
      - Stronger Together, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Triangle Talk, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - GaySource Infoline, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Folder 19)
        Surveys and data collection sheets
      - Center Forums, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Possible Handouts, c. 2001 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous Overheads, Undated (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - Gay Families Overheads, Undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - Fact Sheets, Undated (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - GAGV Topic Header, 1999; FD-27 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - GAGV Topic Header - Disk 2, February 2000; FD-28 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Unlabelled disk (with GAGV Topic Header disks), Undated; FD-29 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Development Committee, 2001-2003 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - Board Meetings 5/12/2003, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Triangle Talk, c. 1998, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Kodak Project, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - GAGV Program Folder, Undated (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - Pride Picnic, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - Breathe life Into Planned Giving - Gill Foundation, Undated (Box 36, Folder 28)
        Participant Workbook
      - Next Step Group, 1999-2003 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - Goals, 2006-2007 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - NYS Dept. of State Change/Amendment, c. 2004 (Box 37, Folder 2)
        For non-profits.
      - Community and Workplace Programming, c. 2006-2007 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Canandaigua National Bank & Trust, c. 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 4)
        Grant proposal for youth program
      - Anti-Violence Program, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 5)
        Grant proposal
      - Luncheon, 2001-2002 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Youth Paperwork, 2005-2006 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Youth Program, c. 2005-2007 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Quotes, Undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
        Overhead projections
      - Examples of Heterosexism, Undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Ally Development, Undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - CASS Model, Undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - First Thoughts, Undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Definitions Sheet, Undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Not So Free To Choose, Undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - GLBT Activist Workshop, 2001-2002 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Speakers Bureau Applications and Confirmation Letters, Undated (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Speakers Bureau Training - '94 Christy's File, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Fliers & News clippings, c. 2007 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - GAGV Board Meetings, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - School District Correspondence, Undated (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - School District Information, 1993-1995 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Action for a Better Community brochures, 1992-1995 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Rochester City School District, c. 1995 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Police Reception, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Political Correspondence, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 26)
        Regarding the "Parental Involvement in Social Issues in Education"
      - Mileage, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Job Objectives/Time Sheets, 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Outreach/Education Coordinator Progress Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Inter-Office Memos, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Fundraising Support, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 31)
      - Faxes, 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 32)
      - Empty Closet Ads Info., Undated (Box 37, Folder 33)
      - Groups (Fact sheets/brochures), 1994 (Box 37, Folder 34)
      - Domestic Violence/Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Curriculum Groups, c. 1995 (Box 37, Folder 35)
      - Auction 1996, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 36)
      - American Express Diversity Board, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 37)
      - Annual Report 94/95, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 38)
      - Quarterly Reports (API), 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 39)
      - Speaker's Bureau Outline Samples, 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 40)
      - Building Community Assets-State of the State Report, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 41)
      - What's at Stake for the GLBT Community in the 2000 Presidential Elections, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 42)
      - Family Pride Coalition House Party Packet, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 43)
      - Lesbian & Gay Rights - An ACLU Report, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 44)
      - Teaching Respect For All - GLSEN Third Annual National Conference, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 45)
      - NYS Dept. of Health Request for Proposals: ACT For Youth, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 46)
      - Workshop Guides - The Campaign To End Homophobia, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 47)
      - "Redistricting and the Gay, Lesbian and Transgender Community", 2001-2002 (Box 37, Folder 49)
        Strategy Memo - the Policy Institute of the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force
      - LAMBDA Network Second Annual Educational Event with Management, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 50)
      - GAGV Demographics Survey, January-March 2002 (Box 37, Folder 51)
      - GAGV Demographics Survey, c. April - September 2002 (Box 37, Folder 52)
      - Making Schools Safer - Book excerpt, Undated (Box 37, Folder 53)
      - GAGV Executive Director's Report, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 54)
      - Boston GLASS Speaker's Bureau, Undated (Box 37, Folder 55)
      - New York State Lesbian and Gay Health and Human Services Network Planning Retreat, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 56)
      - Pride Agenda -- RFP Clinic, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 57)
        Report on health needs of lesbian and gay community in New York.
      - Resource Guide: Dating Violence, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 58)
        Planned Parenthood of the Rochester/Syracuse Region.
      - In Search of Solutions, Undated (Box 37, Folder 59)
        Chapter excerpt "The Session as Intervention"
      - Resources, c. 1994-1998 (Box 37, Folder 60)
        Various fact sheets, reports, web pages.
      - Gill Foundation Annual Report, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 61)
      - ALLY Program Training Materials, Undated (Box 37, Folder 62)
      - Taking the Offensive in the Struggle Against Anti-Gay Abuse in Public Schools: Improving School Policies and State Laws, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 63)
        Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund.
      - Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, Undated (Box 37, Folder 64)
        Various reports.
      - Pink Flamingos and Purple Hearts Convention flier, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 65)
      - Empire State Pride Agenda Foundation, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Events - Invitations and Fliers, 2003-2005 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - GLSEN Leadership Institute - Anti-Homophobia Training Outline, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - MA Dept. of Education - Gay/Straight Alliances Student Guide, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - The Governor’s Commission on Gay & Lesbian Youth Education Report, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 5)
        Boston, MA
      - National Youth Advocacy Coalition, 1997-1999 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Policy Institute of the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force - From Wrongs to Rights, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - National Youth Advocacy Coalition - Policies and Procedures Information Packet, 1993-1998 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - New York Department of Health Grant, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - 04-'05 AVP Legislature Grant, Joseph Robach, c. 2003 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Therapist Survey, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Workplace, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Speakers Bureau Training Material, c. 1994 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Video, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Brighton High School, c. 1995 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - From Hatred to Hope, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Campus Map, Undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Youth Brochure, Undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Tax Exempt Forms, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Thank Yous/Grants, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Medical Literature, c. 1985-1995 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Intake Form (blank), Undated (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Tanya Smolinsky Correspondence, 1994-2002 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Awards, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Volunteerism, c. 2000 (Box 38, Folder 24)
        Projection transparencies.
      - Community Center Building, Undated (Box 38, Folder 25)
        Directions for closing up the community center building
      - Check Request Forms and Time off Forms, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - The Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual & Transgender Community Center Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - National Gay & Lesbian Task Force, 1988, 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - NE Regional Conference, c. 2001-2002 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - Directory of LGBT Services and Resources, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - Department of Education (1), c. 1994, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 31)
        Information/manuals
      - Department of Education (2), c. 1993-1995, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - Dignity for All Students Action Packet, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 33)
      - GAGV Community Center, 2000-2003 (Box 38, Folder 34)
        Presentation Request forms, Board of Directors documents, programs
      - Family & Children, 1998-2002 (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - Gay Pride Picnic, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - GLTB Legal Rights, 2001-2002 (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - GLSEN Training, 2001-2002 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - Answerers Support Services, Undated (Box 38, Folder 39)
        Flier
      - Building Our House, Undated (Box 38, Folder 40)
      - RATFA, Undated (Box 38, Folder 41)
      - Pedtaric Links with the Community Grants Program, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 42)
      - St. John Fisher College, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 43)
      - Speaker's Bureau Correspondence, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 44)
      - Potential Engagement Sites, c. 1992-1995 (Box 38, Folder 45)
      - Film and Video, c. 2002, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 46)
        Contains explicit content.
      - Fliers and Pamphlets, 2002, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 47)
      - New York Civil Liberties Union Annual Report, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 48)
      - Youth Suicide, Undated (Box 38, Folder 49)
      - Green Party of Monroe County, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 50)
      - Adoption Information, c. 1994 (Box 38, Folder 51)
      - Curriculum Council, c. 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 52)
      - Gene Theory Articles, c. 1990-1993 (Box 38, Folder 53)
      - Educators' Training Manuals, 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 54)
      - Workshops, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 55)
      - Dealing with youth in the LGBT Community, c. 1996 (Box 38, Folder 56)
      - LGBT Clients and Patients, c. 1985 (Box 38, Folder 57)
      - Empire State Pride Agenda Lobby Day Participant Packet, 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 58)
      - National Gay & Lesbian Task Force Conference, 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 59)
      - Homophobia, c. 1990 (Box 38, Folder 60)
      - GAGV Non-Profit & Tax Forms, 1973, 1983, 1989-1995, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 61)
        Tanya Smolinsky's copies
      - Programming Survey, Undated (Box 38, Folder 62)
      - Gay Source Info-Line, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 63)
        Statistical Data Sheet
      - Speakers (1), 1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Speakers (2), 1994 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Speakers (3), 1995 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Speakers (4), 1998 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Speakers (5), 1998 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Speakers (6), November-December 2000 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Speakers (7), October 2000 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Speakers (8), March 2000 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Speakers (9), April-May 2000 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Speakers (10), June-September 2000 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Speakers (11), January-February 2000 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Speakers (12), August-October 1996 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Speakers (13), October-December 1996 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Gay Source Info Line, 1994, 1999-2001 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Gay Source Info Line, 1997-1998 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley Board Meeting Agenda, Strategic Plan, Board Roster, etc., 2001-2006 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Organizational Memberships, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Membership Records, 1995-2000 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - GAGV Programming Committee Data, 1998-2003 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - GAGV Board Program Director's Report, 1997-2003 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley "Strategic Planning", 1994-2001 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - GaySource Info-Line Peer Facilitation Program, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - GAGV Membership Survey and results, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Major Membership Drives, 1995-1997 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Fundraising, Etc. Letters, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Fund Development Plan, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Strengthening Ourselves, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Strengthening Ourselves, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Strengthening Ourselves, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Strengthening Ourselves, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Strengthening Ourselves, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Triangle Talk, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Triangle Talk, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Triangle Talk, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Triangle Talk, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Team Rochester, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Gay Health Coalition, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Boy Scouts, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - GAGV Brochure, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Community Education Project, 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Daisy Marquis Jones Foundation Grant, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - First Unitarian Church Grant, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Domestic Partnership, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Team Rochester, 1997-2001 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Empty Closet Committee, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Youth Program Coordinator Hiring, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - LGBTQ Youth Initiative, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - Tanya: To Read 6/26-7/3, undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
        Various articles from 1984-2001
      - Gill Foundation Workshop Schedule/Information on representative Gary Groth, 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Outgiving in Community Gill Foundation Application, 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Organizational Assessment Tool, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Technology Grant – Gill Foundation, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Special Legislation Grant Contract, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - Special Legislative Grant (Dollinger), 2000-2002 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - David Koon: Assemblyman, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - Tides Foundation Grant Application, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Teen Advocacy and Support Services (TASS), 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 30-31)
        Grant applications and support materials
      - Gay Pool, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 32)
      - Monroe Community College: Kristall Nacht, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 33)
      - MLT: Mr. Leatherman Toronto, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 34)
      - North East Regional Pride, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 35)
      - Nazareth College Wilson Cruz, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 36)
      - Radio Program, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 37)
        Lower Power FM service
      - Dr. Laura, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 38)
      - Transgender Equality Handbook, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 39)
      - State Employees Federated Appeal, 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 40)
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 41)
        Includes a program for "Once Upon a December" Holiday concert
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 42)
        Auctions Donations.
      - Sweetheart Ball, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 43)
        Also includes information on budgets, events, marketing
      - Reaching Out: Community Connections Luncheon; 30 Years of Service event - Programs, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 44)
      - Pride Luncheon, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 45)
      - Pride Invite, 2001; CD-2189 (Box 40, Folder 45)
      - GAGV Logic Models, undated (Box 40, Folder 46)
        For all GAGV programming
      - Auction Donations, undated (Box 40, Folder 47)
      - Holiday Open House, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 48)
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 49)
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 50)
        Table Captains
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 58)
        Auction Donations.
      - "Visiting Mr. Green" at JCC Centerstage, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 59)
      - Gayellow Pages, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 60)
      - Vendors: Pride Week, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 61)
      - Marriott Hotel Resorts: marketing, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 62)
      - Brookwood Inn: marketing, undated (Box 40, Folder 63)
      - GAGV marketing folders, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 65)
        For Sweetheart Ball
      - Safe Zone Sticker Project donations, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 66)
      - Pride Picnic, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 67)
      - Samples of Programming Surveys and Questionnaires, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 68)
      - Advertising, newsletters, and event flyers, 1989-2011 (Box 40, Folder 69)
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2000-2002 (Box 41, Folder 1)
        Auction Bid forms, event tickets, and photographs
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 2)
        Love notes/messages, coupons, dance reservations
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 3)
        Ticket reservations
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 4)
        Tax forms, Factsheets and programs
      - Sweetheart Ball, 1999-2002 (Box 41, Folder 5)
        Email, program, budget. Also includes information about the 1999 Sweetheart Ball
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 6)
        Budget, fliers, Agenda etc.
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 7)
        Auction forms, program
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 8)
        Attendees
      - Sweetheart Ball, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 9)
        Expenses
      - Reaching Out: Community Connections Luncheon RSVPs; 30 Years of Service event; Service Award Nomination forms, 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - GAGV Community Education Project (1-5), 2002 (Box 41, Folder 11-15)
        Presentation Request and Evaluation Forms
      - GAGV Board Meeting, April 2003 (Box 35, Folder 1)
        From Box 41, Folder 14
      - Executive Session, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 2)
        From Box 41, Folder 15
      - GAGV Community Education Project (6), 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - GAGV Community Education Project (7), 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - GaySource Info-Line Data Collection, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 18-20)
        Statistical Data Collection Sheets
      - GAGV Speakers Bureau Presentation Evaluations, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 21-22)